

# ANAND KISHORE

## S O F T W A R E T E S T E R



+91 8248858210



https://www.linkedin.com/in/anand-kishore-9b27ba150/

anandkishore2528@gmail.com



8/8, Gandhi Street, Parvathi Nagar, Old Perungalathur, Chennai -600063



anandkishore2528.github.io

Resourceful Software Tester with stellar 4+ years of handling and collaborating with software developers to produce robust, bug-free programs that meet business and consumer needs. Analyzes and improves software development processes and supports teams in meeting critical project deadlines. Captures and documents defects, solutions and test plans accurately and clearly across diverse teams

## EXPERIENCE

#### **QA - SOFTWARE TESTER**

#### **Amazon Development Center India Pvt Ltd**

August 2018 - Present

- Developed and executed QA test cases, scripts and procedures for automated maintenance.
- Operated under Agile and Scrum frameworks to complete releases and well-organized sprints.
- Authored and maintained well-organized, efficient and successful manual test cases for entire team.
- Monitored resolution of bugs, tested fixes and helped developers tackle ongoing problems by providing QA perspective
- Reviewed all test cases and test scripts for quality and identified additional areas to review.
- Tested functional and compatibility of new programs or updates in comparison to existing applications.
- Assessed software bugs and compiled findings along with suggested resolutions for development team members.
- Designed, executed and maintained automated test scripts for in-project deployment.
- Created successful test scripts to manage automated feature testing.
- Completed automation of functional and regression testing.
- Kept scripts and test cases updated with current requirements.

#### QUALITY CONTROLLER

#### Bradman Web Technologies Pvt Ltd

July 2017 - August 2018

- Collaborated with team to test software quality through manual and automated testing.
- Coordinated work with various teams to solve problems and improve efficiency for software testing and automation.
- Verified acceptance by developing and implementing automated and manual application features and regression tests.
- Developed, implemented and maintained automated test ware for scripts, functions and programs to boost testing efficiency.
- Operated under Agile and Scrum frameworks to complete releases and well-organized sprints.
- Carried out tests to identify, report and repair bugs and glitches.
- Built automated test scripts to handle repetitive software testing work.

## EDUCATION

#### BACHELOR IN COMPUTER APPLICATION

Madras University

2021 - 2023

#### DIPLOMA IN COMPUTER TECHNOLOGY

Central Polytechnic College

2024 - 2017

### SECONDARY SCHOOL LEAVING CERTIFICATE

Jai Gopal Garodia National Higher Secondary School

2013 - 2014

#### EXPERTISE

## REGRESSION, FUNCTIONAL & PERFORMANCE TESTING

#### • AUTOMATION & TEST TOOLS

- Selenium/WebDriver
- TestNG
- Maven
- Jenkins

## PRODUCT MANAGEMENT

- Agile
- Scrum
- Jira

#### PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

- Java
- JavaScript
- MySQL
- HTML & CSS

#### DESIGNING

- Web Designing
- Graphic Designing
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Figma

#### SKILLS

#### PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- Working On Agile and Scrum Environments
- Analyzing Requirements Specifications Well
- Test Case Management
- Write Automation Scripts
- Bug Tracking and Resolution
- Cross Browser Compatibility
- Providing Feedback

#### PERSONAL SKILLS

- Smart Working Instead of hard work
- Problem Solving
- Motivation
- Creativity
- Adaptability
- Analytical skills
- Team Work

#### HOBBIES

Playing Cricket

Travelling

Learning About New Technology

Listening Music's

Freelancing